...TO FIND THE MISSING EVIDENCE THAT WILL PROVE HIS INNOCENCE...
The Last Chance is a drama film directed by Thomas Bentley.
Alan Burmister leaves Devon on a secret gun-running expedition immediately after his engagement to Mary Perrin is
announced; he returns at Christmas to find himself accused of the murder of Ivor Connel, a moneylender.
Mary's father had always hoped that his daughter would
marry John Worrall, a rising barrister.
Worrall is briefed for the defence, but when he loses the case and Alan is condemned to penal servitude for life,
no one but the judge realises that he has not made use of the best piece of defence evidence...
Mary Perrin, played by Judy Kelly.
Alan Burmister, played by Frank Leighton.
John Worrall, played by Wyndham Goldie.
Judge Croyle, played by Aubrey Mallalieu.
Michael Worrall, played by Billy Milton.
Mr. Perrin, played by Laurence Hanray.
The Last Chance is a 1937 British drama film directed by Thomas Bentley and
starring Frank Leighton, Judy Kelly and Laurence Hanray.
Its plot involves a gunrunner who makes a jail break in order to
gather evidence to prove he is innocent of murder.
It was made as a supporting feature at British
International Pictures' second studio at Welwyn.
The film's sets were designed by the art director Duncan Sutherland.
The tone is emotional.